Once upon a time, there was a girl who loved flowers more than anyone.
She prayed every day for the whole town to be filled with beautiful flowers.
To make that happen, she pulled up all the town's ugly weeds.
Eventually, the girl's prayers were answered, and the town was blanketed in flowers.
But they say the town that was filled with innumerable blossoms of every color imaginable somehow looked gray.
Roo? Are you there?
Roo...
Roo came back looking like her usual self again. Not at all like Krehi, but there's something different. Could she really be Krehi after all?
Is it Krehi's fault that Muto tried to take PK's heart from her? Is something happening behind the scenes where I can't see it?
I don't want to fight anymore.
Say, why don't you fight one more time?
No!
But chances like this are rare. A magnificent battle would be...
Forget it!
I mean, you know, sure I was into Muto for a time, but frankly, my passion has cooled. At this point, I really don't care all that much. In the end, I've always been a Fakir girl!
Yeah, he's definitely been cool lately, hasn't he?
Like that air of mystery.
The air of his shady crook.
And that slightly dark aura.
Oh yeah, the gloomy mood.
Want a battle?
Bring it on.
No!
Come on guys, a battle!
Have you become a Fakir girl too?
A three-way fight!
No, no, no, no way!
I'm saying I don't like fighting. I mean, you two shouldn't fight!
Huh?
I would have thought too.
Wow.
How's it fine?
Oh, so divine.
I feel so sad.
Why did she hurt?
What? The Muto is so wonderful.
If he buried me like that, getting hurt might not be so bad.
I would have thought too.
How's it fine?
Uh...
Hey, uh...
Oh...
I have divine news for all you ladies.
The Gold Crown Academy Fine Arts Week starts tomorrow,
and Mr. Muto says that whoever wins this ballet contest,
he will make her his partner in the exhibition in place of Miss Rue,
who is injured and unable to dance.
Don't rejoice yet, ladies. I haven't finished.
The runner-up will have the incredibly desirable opportunity
to be my partner.
What's more, my life partner.
Yes, a marriage.
Marriage!
Viva ma-
I understand.
This must mean everyone is aiming for runner-up
and has begun practicing hard right away!
Muto and Rue, I thought I saw him go this way.
It's not so easy pretending to be injured.
Pretending? Then she lied?
So do it right this time.
I know, Krehii.
Krehii?
He called her Krehii.
Muto.
Blue Prittalee, you too. And you too.
Wow!
Oh, I'm really sorry. I didn't mean to intrude.
It's fine. This garden belongs to everybody.
So pretty.
Aren't they?
I didn't mean that.
Oh, I mean, of course the flowers are pretty.
But you know, that's not all, Miss...
My name's Freya.
Oh, my name is Deck. This is amazing.
Did you grow all these flowers, Miss Freya?
Flowers bloom on their own.
I simply pray.
Bloom prittalee, bloom abundantly.
Say, why aren't you practicing right now like everyone else?
For the art festival competition?
Yeah.
I like ballet just like you do. So I will practice later.
First, I must care for these little ones.
Wow, you really love flowers, don't you?
Yes, well, it would be wonderful if the world were full of flowers, wouldn't it?
Miss Freya is what's wonderful. It makes me wish I could become Miss Wonderful. But I...
You don't have it, Zora!
What? Really?
Really, Zora!
Not at all?
Not at all, Zora!
Wait, who's there?
It's not here, Zora!
Where did you hide it, Zora?
Huh?
What's not?
Your duck's tail, Zora!
What?
What do you mean, duck?
Where is it, Zora?
Quack!
Oh!
What?
Qu...
Ah!
Oh, you're a duck, Zora!
Oh!
There's your tail, Zora!
Quack!
Ah!
Oh, just who was that kid anyway?
Thanks to her, I was late.
Now I have detention.
New York?
Huh?
That voice is...
I'm not really hoping to win.
It's her.
It is Miss Freya.
Do you hate me?
And Muto?
Of course not.
Your beautiful heart makes beautiful flowers bloom.
If we put our abilities together,
I'm sure we could make a new kind of flower bloom that no one's ever seen.
Nobody else has a heart so beautiful
as to have the desire to make the world happy with dancing and flowers.
Surely even you believe that, don't you?
I can't say I ever...
It's all right to think that.
Because you're different from all those nobodies.
And you'll win the competition.
That's right.
Everyone around you is your enemy.
Love only me and hate everyone else.
Yes.
Promise to love only me.
All right.
Promise me that you'll hate everyone else.
I will.
I promise to love only you.
And to hate everyone else, too.
Not again!
These blues!
The room is full of flowers we've never seen before.
Isn't it, Muto?
Miss Freya, will you hate everyone?
But the real you doesn't want to hate even one person, does she?
No, but Muto says that he desires it, so…
Tutu, help me!
Muto?
still hasn't soaked you through?
Hurry up and become my prince and mine alone.
The prince who loves me and me alone.
The story is progressing deeply, quietly,
in a place where little Doc can't see it.
We will be opening the ballet competition momentarily.
As announced previously,
the winner will dance with Mr. Muto as his partner.
Oh, it's so nice!
The runner-up, of course,
will have the privilege and pleasure
of dancing eternally as my partner!
Oh!
The participants must be feeling a nervousness
such as they've never felt before.
That's for sure.
Well, if they win, it's heaven.
But if they make one false step, it's hell.
With that, let us now begin the competition.
Everybody try your best aiming
for this much-coveted runner-up bouquet!
The wonderful Muto is watching.
I don't want to lose.
No matter what.
The ones to become his partner
will be me.
The tension's suffocating.
Oh, I wish Doc could have been in the contest, too.
Actually, where is Doc?
What?
Does she not care at all
who becomes the wonderful Muto's partner?
Does that mean she's completely become
a Fakir girl now?
Ah!
I sense a battle!
Come on.
Muto probably can't do anything funny
during the contest.
I'm kinda just showing up.
I hope Fakir will be hung.
Whoa!
Oh!
Hey!
Ooh!
Hey, what are you doing here?
Ooh.
Fakir.
Fakir!
Huh?
I-i-eh-i-k-e-k-eh-k-k-k-k-k- saw you,다고-k-k-k-k-k-k- votre z és-k-k incredible!
G-k-k-k-k-k-k-k yo-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k
o-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k-k!
Oh!
Her neck!
Hey!
Her neck just twisted.
It twisted her neck.
She twisted around.
Why are you hiding, Zura?
Shut up! Here.
Alright now, have you at least calmed down a little bit?
Yes, thank you.
Who is she?
Well, her name is Usura.
Karan.
He made her from the wood from Eidol that didn't burn up.
From Miss Eidol?
Oh, so is that why she knew me already?
What? No, I told her about you.
Huh?
I told her about you and Mewtwo and things.
But it looks like Eidol's memories are gone.
She warmed my body and became a guiding flame for you and Mewtwo.
Miss Eidol.
She really did save our lives that night.
Even like this.
I'm glad I get to see her again.
Now that you say it, she kind of does remind me.
Oh!
Quack!
How'd you do, Zura?
Just shut up.
Anyway, Duck, didn't you have some reason for coming?
Yes, it has to do with Mewtwo.
A few days ago, he tried to take Pique's heart out.
It didn't work though, so now he's trying to do the same thing to Miss Freya.
The hard shard of love that Princess Tutu gave back to him,
that shard was soaked in a bath of the raven's blood.
So, he'll love only me, and he'll find a young and beautiful heart for my father and give it to him as a sacrifice.
Did you tell Tutu about all this?
I should. If I did that, I could make her suffer, couldn't I?
So, what do you think happened to Mewtwo? Find out anything?
No, nothing.
Well, alright. That's all. I just thought you might have found out something, so I came to see if you had.
Right.
I'm worried about Miss Freya, so I'm gonna go back.
Wait! I think I'll go with you.
Uzura, I'm leaving you to house it.
Leave it to me, Uzura!
Let's go.
Great.
Adel?
I don't get it, Uzura!
This is no good.
The dancing's fine, but their expressions don't work.
As it stands, there's no one who qualifies for winner or runner-up.
Next contestant.
What novel dancing.
Above all, she has great expressions.
Put her on the shortlist.
Next, please.
Oh, it looks like a victory.
Has been decided.
Oh, no.
You mean the runner-up?
Please make her the runner-up.
Very soon now, Father.
What a lovely fragrance.
I can smell the sweet scent from here.
I can hardly stand it.
This time, I will most certainly bring to you a heart that shines blackly, Father.
And that will be the time when your efforts shall reap their reward, my daughter.
Yes, dear Father.
Leave Mewtwo to me.
You need to save Freya.
But if we just talk to Mewtwo…
You need to do as I tell you.
Alright.
Blonde, she's the winner!
Yes!
Congratulations, Freya.
My love belongs to you.
So, she really did win.
Which means the runner-up!
Okay.
Unfortunately, this year, no one called mine to runner-up.
And with that, I declare the competition over!
It's over.
Oh, that's right!
Hey!
Love only me, Freya.
I want you to hate everybody else.
Your heart is young and beautiful, dyed black.
It gives off a strong fragrance.
You'll give it to me, won't you?
I will.
Dance, Freya.
Dance is proof of your love for me, and give me your heart!
Miss Freya!
Back here!
Wait.
Please, come dance with me.
Miss Freya.
Huh?
Too...
Quit showing your face.
Hurry and vanish.
Again?
You would try to come between Muto and me?
I won't have it!
Miss Freya!
Yes.
That's it, my little flower.
Come into my arms, Freya.
Pull yourself together, Muto!
Miss Freya.
Is that love real?
Weren't flowers your hope, your prayer, your wish?
You're right.
That is what I desire, what I pray for.
Now look around.
See how many have bloomed?
Is this really what you wanted them to look like?
Listen closely to the voices of the flowers you loved.
The flowers?
Voices?
I can't!
I can't hear them!
Watch!
Watch Tutu's dance!
I can't hear them!
I can't hear the flowers' voices!
Don't give up.
Remember.
Remember your prayer.
My prayer!
Yes.
Your prayer for everybody to be happy.
You need to be happy.
That was what you wished for, wasn't it, Miss Freya?
Oh, I hear them!
The flowers' voices!
Muto, remember!
Why won't you love me?
Fine!
Muto!
Remember your real self!
My real self?
Don't let your ears be poisoned by some knight too selfish to die.
Grehi!
The way you are now is the real Muto.
What have you done to Muto?
The one who made the prince like this is you, Tutu.
Stop it!
After all, you returned the feeling of love to the prince, ignorant of the fact that it was
dyed in the raven's blood.
You didn't tell her, Fakir.
I'm forever in your debt, Tutu!
I'm forever in your debt, Tutu.
Muto.
Hey, are you angry with me because I kept it from you?
A little.
I'm sorry, Doc.
Muto is Muto, right?
Even with Raven's blood in him, Muto's Muto.
He'll go back to his old self, right?
Of course.
Uzura's waiting for us.
You be careful of Uzura.
Congratulations, little Doc.
Now there's one less thing you don't know.
But perhaps ignorance was better.
I am qualified to be a true prince, one who loves everyone, and is also loved by everyone.
I already told you there is no Rue.
That's not true. I don't believe that. I get this feeling you're still Rue.
Promise to love only me, hate everyone else.
When people say duck goes well together and is lovey-dovey, what's it mean, Sora?
What duck is? With whom?
A feeling expressed without even a word.
That's the mime for I love you.
All you children who love stories, come gather round.